{
    "name": "U.S. Government",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the head of the executive branch of the United States government?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "The President",
            "answers": [
                "The President",
                "The Speaker of the House",
                "The Supreme Court Chief Justice",
                "The Senate Majority Leader"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many voting members are there in the United States Congress?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "535",
            "answers": [
                "535",
                "515",
                "143",
                "432"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the final step before a bill becomes a law in the United States?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "The President Signs the Bill",
            "answers": [
                "The President Signs the Bill",
                "The Senate Approves the Bill",
                "The House Debates the Bill",
                "The Supreme Court Reviews the Bill"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the primary function of the Judicial Branch of the United States government?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Interpret Laws",
            "answers": [
                "Interpret Laws",
                "Write Laws",
                "Veto Laws",
                "Enforce Laws"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many houses are in the U.S. legislative branch?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Two",
            "answers": [
                "Two",
                "One",
                "Three",
                "Four"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "How many senators does each state in the United States have in the Senate?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Two",
            "answers": [
                "Two",
                "One",
                "Three",
                "Four"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who makes up the legislative branch?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "House and Senate",
            "answers": [
                "House and Senate",
                "The President",
                "The Supreme Court",
                "The Vice President"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What form of government does the United States have?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "Federal Republic",
            "answers": [
                "Federal Republic",
                "Monarchy",
                "Communist",
                "Socialist"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the first 10 amendments called?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "The Bill of Rights",
            "answers": [
                "The Bill of Rights",
                "The Bill of Tens",
                "The Commandments",
                "The Constitution"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first person to sign the Constitution?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "George Washington",
            "answers": [
                "George Washington",
                "Thomas Jefferson",
                "Benjamin Franklin",
                "James Madison"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who wrote the original Bill of Rights?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "James Madison",
            "answers": [
                "James Madison",
                "Benjamin Franklin",
                "George Washington",
                "Thomas Jefferson"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What document did the Constitution replace?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "The Articles Of Confederation",
            "answers": [
                "The Articles Of Confederation",
                "The Bill of Rights",
                "The Emancipation Proclamation",
                "The Civil Rights Act of 1870"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the purpose of The Federalist Papers?",
            "type": "multi",
            "correct": "To Urge The Ratification of The United States Constitution",
            "answers": [
                "To Urge The Ratification of The United States Constitution",
                "To Prevent War With Britain",
                "To Raise Taxes",
                "To Form the Union Army"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "id": 1707521113378
}